{
    "subject": "resource/Kwararafa",
    "predicate": "property/capital",
    "object": "resource/Wukari",
    "human_readable": "Kwararafa's capital is Wukari.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8854596018791199,
            "question": "Which kingdom has Wukari as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8125202059745789,
            "question": "What is the capital of Kwararafa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7193560004234314,
            "question": "Is Wukari a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6100117564201355,
            "question": "Where is Wukari located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4593116044998169,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks or sites in Wukari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3379300832748413,
            "question": "What are some historical facts about Kwararafa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31229445338249207,
            "question": "Who were the rulers of Kwararafa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2955663502216339,
            "question": "What are the main industries or economic activities in Wukari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2690604627132416,
            "question": "What is the significance of Kwararafa in history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26570868492126465,
            "question": "How has Kwararafa influenced neighboring cultures?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kwararafa's capital is Wukari.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7037_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of Kwararafa in history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7037_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the main industries or economic activities in Wukari?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7037_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the rulers of Kwararafa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7037_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7037_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, it is mentioned that \"Before it became a fully-fledged federation, [Kwararafa] was widely referred to as the capital of Kwararafa.\" and \"it has been reduced to the status of a town in the present-day Taraba state of Nigeria\" which implies that Wukari was the capital of Kwararafa."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that supports the statement \"Kwararafa's capital is Wukari.\" Specifically, the document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7037/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt mentions \"Before it became a fully-fledged federation, it was widely referred to as the capital of Kwararafa\" and later states that Wukari \"status as a successor federation to Kwararafa was because of its influential role of capital during the Kwararafa era.\" This information directly supports the claim."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}